I won't work overtime today
本宫今天不加班
Episode 2
第二集
Mr. Li
李总
Do you drink water
您喝水吗
I'm sorry, Mr. Li
对不起 李总
Let me wipe it for you
我给您擦一下
What's going on
怎么回事
Why are you stumbling me
你为什么要绊我呀
I'm sorry
对不起啊
Don't move
别动
Thank you
谢谢
Emperor
皇
I handle it myself
我自己处理
You guys work
你们工作吧
Mr. Li, I'll see you off
李总 我送您
I hired you to come
我聘请你来
Is it specifically for me
是专门送我的吗
My hands are slender and long
我这手又细又长
And a faint fragrance
还有淡淡的清香
What is she doing
她在干吗
Want to use this method
想用这种方法
Caught my attention
引起我的注意
Scattered, scattered, scattered
散了散了散了
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
Just wait for me
给我等着
After all, living under the eaves
毕竟活在屋檐下
Still have to control your emotions
还是要控制自己的情绪
But it's so cool
不过 可真爽
So my name is He Jiaojiao
原来我叫何皎皎
Dwelling in
居住在
Room 301, 18 Orange Tseng Road
橘井路18号301室
Mobile Number
手机号码
Photocopied papers are laid on the table
复印的文件放在桌上
I don't know to send it to everyone
不知道发给大家
You changed your abacus
你是算盘变的
Dial it and move it
拨一下动一下
What do you do
干什么
Give me another stare and try
再瞪我一下试试
Sister Jing
静姐
I'm going right now
我这就去
The last document
最后一份文件
It's actually for him
竟然是给他的
In ancient times, there was a king of Yue who slept down and tried his courage
古有越王卧薪尝胆
The existing bright moon contains dirt and endurance
现有明月含垢忍屈
Not yet
现在还不是
When dealing with him
对付他的时候
Enter
进
Put your stuff there
东西放那吧
Give me the clothes
衣服给我
How can it be you
怎 怎么是你
It's not Special Assistant Xu
不是许特助
Can you send me clothes
给我送衣服吗
I'm sorry, Mr. Li
对不起 李总
I'm here to deliver documents
我是来送文件的
Then why didn't you tell me earlier
那你怎么不早说
I want to say
我想说
But you take it off more urgently
可是您脱的比较迫切
I think you did it on purpose
我看你就是故意的吧
Deliberately wanted to see me
故意想看我
Can you not
你能不能不要
I feel so good about myself
这么自我感觉良好啊
You, you, you still dare to get started
你你 你还敢上手
That's it
就这
Practice again
再练练吧
And I'm not interested in you
而且我对你没有兴趣
Mr. Li, your
李总 您的
You
你
Clothes
衣服
Get closer
靠近一些
Feed me
喂我
I actually
我居然
I was really fascinated by him
还真的被他迷住过
It's really unbearable to look back
真是不堪回首
It takes so long to send a file
发个文件也要这么久
Take this file and print it
这个文件拿去打印一下
Three minutes later I'm going to
三分钟之后我就要
He Jiaojiao adds watermark
何皎皎 加水印
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
What are you still doing
你还愣着干吗呀
Why don't you go and collect the express delivery
还不去把快递收了
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
Go turn off the air conditioner
去关一下空调吧
Thanks for hard work
辛苦喽
What the hell is this
这什么玩意
Dark
黑不溜秋的
Is this drinkable
这能喝吗
Coffee
咖啡
Don't give it to me again
你以后别再给我
What kind of coffee are you drinking
喝这什么咖啡了
Drinking the West Lake Longjing used to paying tribute
喝惯了进贡的西湖龙井
I really can't get used to this
这个真的喝不惯
Gong Gong Tea
贡 贡茶
Where can I get it for you
我 我去哪给你弄去
Then make do
那就凑合
Find me some white water
给我找点白水吧
It's really not as good as before
真是比不上从前
Sister Jiaojiao
皎皎姐
You're talking nonsense again
你又在胡说八道了
Sister Jing, she is very narrow-minded
静姐她很小心眼的
She's targeting you like this today
她今天这样针对你
You don't worry about the future
你就不担心以后
Just her
就她
Casually
随随便便
I have a hundred ways to get her
我有一百种方法弄她
Off work
下班了
Well, can we go now
那我们是不是可以走了
We can't go
我们不能走
We have to work overtime
我们得加班
Why
为什么
Because
因为
Because there is a kind of overtime
因为有种加班
It's called the leader hasn't got off work yet
叫做领导还没下班
And some kind of overtime
还有种加班
It's called a leader looking for trouble temporarily
叫做领导临时找事
Survival in the workplace food chain
生存在职场食物链
We at the bottom
最底端的我们
There is no right to choose
是没有选择权利的
We
我们
Here it is
在这呢
They all feel very leisure, don't they
都觉得很闲是吧
I'm done with ours
我 我们的都做完了
That's just right
那正好
I'll give you some information later
一会儿给你们一些资料
You guys sort it out
你们整理好
And then what
然后呢
Scan another electronic file
再扫描一个电子档
Re-use table statistical summary
再用表格统计汇总
Send me email
发我邮箱
I want to review tomorrow
明天我要审核
Let me tell you
我说吧
It must be done within today
今天之内必须做完
I want to see tomorrow
明天我要看到
What if I can't finish it
要是我做不完呢
Then you can resign yourself on your own initiative
那你就自己主动辞职吧
Our company doesn't need waste
我们公司不需要废物
Just a quiet concubine
区区一个静嫔
You dare to shout and drink at me
都敢对我呼来喝去的了
Put her on hold for a few days
暂且缓她几天
Empress Zhao Concubine
赵嫔娘娘
To spare you the death penalty
免了你们的死罪
But you bumped into her
但你们冲撞了她
Tonight you guys
今晚你们
We need to put this warehouse
就要把这个仓库
It's all sorted out
都整理好
Mammy
嬷嬷
How can I finish this night
这一晚上怎么做得完呀
That's your business
那是你们的事
Let you have a long memory
让你们好好长长记性
Sister Mingmingyue, don't be afraid
明 明月姐 你别怕
I, I protect you
我 我保护你
Good
好
Then what are you shaking
那你抖什么呀
Let's get started
我们开始吧
Start sorting out the big items first
先从大件的开始整理
It's faster this way
这样比较快一点
Sister Mingyue
明月姐
I'm sorry
对不起啊
I'm the one who got you into trouble
是我连累了你
It's okay
没事
We can do it
我们可以的
Refuel
加油
Come on
来吧
It seems that no matter where
看来无论在哪里
If you are weak, you will be bullied
弱小就会被人欺负
Sister Jiaojiao
皎皎姐
Do you like watching the sunrise
你喜欢看日出吗
Why do you ask
为什么这么问
According to this posture
按照这样的架势
We can't finish it tomorrow morning
咱们明天早上都做不完
It's okay
没事
The less likely it seems
看似越不可能
Things accomplished
完成的事情
The more you complete it, the more meaningful it is
越完成越有意义
We can do it
我们可以的
And
而且
Watch the sunrise with you
跟你一起看日出
Very happy too
也很开心啊
Finally done
终于做完了
Sister Mingyue, look
明月姐 你看
Sunrise
日出
Komatsu, do you believe it
小松 你相信吗
One day
总有一天
I'll take you there
我会带你去
The highest place in the city
这城里最高的地方
Watch the sunrise
看日出
Finally finished
终于整理完了
Sister Jiaojiao
皎皎姐
Why are you so fast
你怎么这么快
This is compared to
这和比起
Compared with organizing the palace warehouse
整理皇宫仓库比起来
It's too simple
简单太多了
I'll do it
我来吧
Just in time for you to teach me
正好你来教教我
How to build an electronic file
怎么建电子档
Good
好
Watch this
看 点这个
Sent out
发出去了
But email and wechat
但是邮箱和微信
Sister Jing didn't even reply to me
静姐都没有回我
I think she should be asleep
我觉得她应该睡着了
Both now
现在都
It's eleven o'clock
十一点了
We often
我们经常
Do you work overtime so late
加班到这么晚吗
We interns
我们实习生啊
This is the company
就是这公司
The lowest level of workers
最底层的劳动者
Any regular employee
随便哪个正式员工
Can be exploited
都可以剥削
Especially those like Sister Jing
尤其像静姐那样子的
Relying on my years of qualifications
仗着自己有几年的资历
All her work
她的所有工作
It's all done by interns
全是实习生干
Looks like we can't keep her
看来不能留她了
Pick me up downstairs in five minutes
五分钟后 楼下接我
We're supposed to be this company
我们应该是这个公司
Is it the latest person to get off work?
下班最晚的人了吧
That's not necessarily true
那可不一定
Maybe Mr. Li is still here
说不定李总还在呢
He works overtime until late every time
他每次都加班到很晚
Is it
是吗
Sister Jiaojiao
皎皎姐
It's so late
都这么晚了
Or else
要不
Come on, I'll take you back
走 我送你回去
Let me take you back
我送你回去吧
You take me back
你送我回去
You forgot everything
你什么都忘记了
Do you remember
你还记得
Where is Orange Well Road
橘井路在哪吗
I'm just not familiar with
我只是不熟悉
It's not like you're stupid
又不是傻了
All right, let's go
行了 走吧
Then I'm leaving
那我走了
Don't worry
放心放心
Honk the horn
按一下喇叭
No matter how powerful
再厉害
She's just a little girl
也不过是个小姑娘
How can there be such a good-looking person
怎么会有这么好看的人
Why hasn't Sister Jiaojiao come yet
皎皎姐怎么还没来
Everyone saw it
大家都看到了
Dare to be late during the internship period
实习期就敢迟到
Good morning, Sister Jing
早呀 静姐
Are you doing anything
你有事吗
Why are you only coming to work now
你怎么现在才来上班
It's eight fifty-nine
现在是八点五十九分
Working time is nine o'clock in the morning
上班时间是早上九点
I'm just in time
我正好赶来
Is there a problem
有问题吗
What about yesterday's work? Give me
昨天的工作呢 给我
Sister Jing
静姐
I advise you to return your
我劝您回您的
Take a look at the work station
工位上看一看
If you open the mailbox
如果您打开邮箱
There should be an answer
应该会有答案
Yeah, yeah
对啊
I sent your email yesterday
昨天发你邮箱了
But you didn't reply
但你没回
The information is on your desk, too
资料也放你桌上了
Sister Jing
静姐
Very good
很好
You two better not
你们两个最好不要
What's wrong with me
给我出什么纰漏啊
Go make me a cup of coffee
去给我泡杯咖啡
Are you sure
你确定
Go ahead
去啊
What are you talking about?
磨叽什么
It really is
真的是
We're not servants
我们又不是下人
Make coffee and call us
泡个咖啡还要使唤我们
It will be very bitter if you soak so much
你泡这么多会很苦的
Is it
是吗
I'd better make a new cup
我还是重新泡一杯吧
No need
不用了
I'll do it
我来吧
Sister Jiaojiao
皎皎姐
Sister Jing, she really goes too far
静姐她确实很过分
But you early in the morning
但是你一早
Talk to her like that
跟她这么说话
She's already very unhappy
她已经很不开心了
She'll definitely be picky about coffee
她肯定会挑剔咖啡的
You pissed her off like this
你这样子惹怒她
So what
所以呢
As if she couldn't do anything
好像 她也不能怎么样
Let's walk straight and sit straight
咱们行得正 坐得直
There's nothing to be afraid of
就没什么可怕的
Besides, if you get angry, just get angry
再说惹怒就惹怒呗
Wait for her to bite the hook
等她咬钩